salad on there didn't you you got the is
it greens coming is it on green gone
greens are gone wa you know many fries
he had on the
tray none
no find out when he comes back that
three no did you have any on the train
no no
[Music]
Kevin Kevin
CH not the
what
happened past what this
why okay cot tap you in there off
[Music]
you
fire yeah
okay keep it nice and
clean okay so one furger two fries one
Greens on M can you do the floor for me
please do the
floor these all horse bu
make sure we clean this when we using it
yeah thank you
M
C thank you
mus ready for me
bro
105 are these are these buns branded
this
morning could do it being a little bit
clearer
the brand you need to make sure it's
washed before you do it wash with a wire
brush the BR the Brer you know the end
it builds up with carbon on it so just
brush it with the wire
thing your M thank
you 4
fire table four and need to turn the
table thick
enough
surprise service
boot all of it going to beable six
right so next up we're going to go two
burgers and a lunch steak you
we and when I say lunch I mean
pre-theater in the back
SE table four spirate they need to turn
the table yeah I just got 25 25
hold
82 yeah they're done but go slowly on
82 25 is three in the cards head
he hopefully it'll be there by the time
we get it after this we're going to go
table four
please
and I need cauliflower I need two old
day Chef yeah rush or no rush uh no
rush I'll take with the two pork I'll
take two cauliflower
please luy two fries they were six thank
you are they missing
a looks like they're waiting for another
dish on
six you want to double check yeah
the maybe
not they look happy yeah this looked a
bit weird at the start I think they're
okay no it's
right I'll hold it
eight will prob next in line
Jack 26 as well
yes
[Music]
105 Fus 30 seconds there Angelo
let's go one
table day
[Music]
see how much better that is
yeah H it's beautiful it looks sexy so
before I
[Music]
my S SP
yes okay so two pork two cauliflower now
wait the corn it's the last of my CIF P
okay
yeah 42
polow is needed
yeah huh you need more for no size p no
I got I got these two any more we'll
need more okay
[Music]
here how are you
sh you go
[Music]
nice p is coming
up bit heavy on the seasoning that
[Music]
these both are starters yes chef
42 nothing
you okay you s space
both of those for
start 73 with a cauliflower you want to
grab cabbage cabbage cauliflower 73
grabbing a tray
73 73 on both yes George 73 cabbage
cauliflower gone I've got a second
cauliflower here Chef
yeah cauliflower is going to table three
table three yes yeah
42 with the corn
going anything else for the 40s
45 45 43 42
42 want to follow on
45 Okay so
8225 next please
[Music]
four no one just one to
four two is it two sorry CHF
[Music]
two one have one doesn't
have uh say again how would you like the
L so mushrooms leaks put a few leaks and
a few Che there keep it dry like a tiny
bit of the musom not too wet yeah
what's the garnish to the lamb shank on
the menu you say herb cream or horse her
her her cream myi leak and peas but not
an ulion
apparently that's what George told me at
least after this we're going to go
26 105 if you're ready
ready 26 105 after that table
eight
table 45 already had it
I so one fries I need yeah l
pink fur got added on with 2 yes chef
drop one ping for Rush
order you also have the street fire here
[Music]
two1 eat a slow yeah e slow
Che
o very slow
Chef we got a little push now coming
okay go add on 113 to
eight just a mushroom burger
Jack 23 may be ready before
2011 uh yeah no mil
want me
I me
[Music]
one fire
I'm going to put it with the other
straight fire burer on 113
deck okay start carving the fet straight
behind
you so need one pink fur that's nice the
next up you got one fries one furg yes
flam shine coming up h
who right taking 25 Jack oh yeah
uh lovely lamb
sh going to add on 203 as well so we go
3 SP phow Burger now after that you're
going to do
this and the phow burger
okay who lose all the marbles from the
ticket runner on the one in the back
yeah
three on
[Music]
and next table Yeah I need uh a beef rib
a muscle and an octopus yeah beef rib
muscle
octopus okay
[Music]
Jazzy
wait got my first rodeo here
okay so you've got
Burger you got halber two F Burger pork
vanison thank you
how's
the is that uh
is that a 104 or is that
a
huh 104 is that
actually you're baffling me I don't know
what you're talking
about is that a big VIP
no yes
dear right6 and 105
okay so you got the rare one here rare
medium rare you got my fries please
Angelo
yes
George
table table three I'm
going um they have color not yet
H got the burger
ready behind you hot
there you
go okay rare on your
right
andet hold the line
[Music]
105 I need burger place bro Burger
okay venison pork halber three burgers
yes
three after this
Jun I got it don't worry
24 73 easy
table Sean how's seven looking what is
seven
Che why here
goer right nice one boys keep it
up
23 thank you for you for here yeah can I
get one bread
Adam Jasmine though
one bread for me for the main Jack 23
and 24 will be 421 I just moved them
around ever touch my Check Yes Yes W do
it
again hey this PO guard is looking
beautiful uh
Angelo very nice
you got to support
[Music]
one more Master fire
did they bring you Burger PL in the no
[Music]
way let's go 109
20898 a little bit more next time a
little bit more only a little bit
though I'm going to go table Muses
muscles
Hal table eight oh amazing
yeah okay I'm waiting on three fries
Angelo yes
hold Chef hold
sorry tell
me two on 46 one on
[Music]
another just the fries yeah three total
five
yes one pork table eight
please okay you got the next round yeah
mushroom B
[Music]
yeah 113 on the
r
mus
113 that not 113 amazing that's 203
though
sh in
perfect nice work so next up you're
going to do lunch menu steaks and one
cauliflower yes and then you've got a f
Burger as well
okay nice and easy
203 running
three it all of that is table eight okay
have you sent the o to eight coming
right that's the last thing
okay the octopus yeah just the
octopus seven seven yes
113 already got bread 113 already got
their
bread 109
[Music]
109 so plow three steak and a burger
after that we got 23
42 I need the cauliflower puree for this
table
you need anything from me Chef no yet uh
not yet I'm all good for the moment C
uh for four minutes please one
C you
don't forget the pepper on the
cauliflower
please you got one more SL of beef
please all right
sure Che this part is going to table 49
please 49 Crossing as well
check 2011 is the way
wait want the way ticket or yes
please right CH are going to table 75
okay
service actually sorry I'm not ready yes
sure
holding 2011 fireing Jack
wait you got the ticket
yeah yes
yeah how long on fries
[Music]
from you and one for the main so three
all day
dear
Mom hey it's me I'm still here in
London
yeah I
right Sid's
[Music]
coming two Fri one pink
fur pink fur
in let's go
come fries 10 seconds ping fur 1
[Music]
minute don't double Bur
you coming for
me right a little not scrub didn't have
much a lot of green tonight
we need yeah one coming
for okay next up 201
7 2011
457 after that
49 you have that it's a
79 and and a cauliflower
still missing one fries one pink fur no
the fries there was one with the burger
one with the steak and one with the
yeah Chef need a c no hold keep
going super
quick just one yeah
Mayo Mayo
then thank you and then Qui
so you should have one more fries
now and one pink F now as well
and know that one is that one we
have got one more in one more each in y
but
mold butter multi make